{
  "exercises": [
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0646\u0627",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "sentence_en": "Here is good",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "question": " \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0647\u0646\u0627 \u062c\u064a\u062f",
      "sentence_en": "Here is good",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0647\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "sentence_en": "I will pay cash",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u064a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "question": " \u0647\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0647\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0643\u0627\u0634",
      "sentence_en": "I will pay cash",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0645"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u062f\u064a",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u062f\u064a",
      "sentence_en": "I like the music",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632",
      "question": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u062f\u064a",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u062f\u064a",
      "sentence_en": "I like the music",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0634"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629",
      "question": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062f\u064a",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u062f\u064a",
      "sentence_en": "I like the music",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u064a",
      "question": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u063a\u0646\u064a\u0629 \u062f\u064a",
      "sentence_en": "I like the music",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0634\u063a\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u062a\u0634\u063a\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Can you turn on the AC?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u063a\u0644",
      "question": " \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u062a\u0634\u063a\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Can you turn on the AC?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641",
      "question": " \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u062a\u0634\u063a\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u062a\u0634\u063a\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Can you turn on the AC?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Can I pay with VISA?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "question": " \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Can I pay with VISA?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0641\u0648"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627",
      "question": " \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Can I pay with VISA?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0634",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0645\u0634 \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645",
      "sentence_en": "I don't understand",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u064a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645",
      "question": " \u0645\u0634 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0645\u0634 \u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645",
      "sentence_en": "I don't understand",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0634"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a \u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "sentence_en": "My Arabic is very bad",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629",
      "question": " \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a \u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "sentence_en": "My Arabic is very bad",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u0627",
      "question": " \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a \u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u064b",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u062a\u064a \u0633\u064a\u0626\u0629 \u062c\u062f\u0627\u064b",
      "sentence_en": "My Arabic is very bad",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0641\u0648",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f\u064b\u0627",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0639\u0641\u0648\u064b\u0627",
      "sentence_en": "Excuse Me",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0634"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "sentence_en": "I'm learning Arabic",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645",
      "question": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "sentence_en": "I'm learning Arabic",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "question": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "sentence_en": "I'm learning Arabic",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Can you repeat that?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627",
      "question": " \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062a\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Can you repeat that?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0643\u0631"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Can you speak slower, please?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621",
      "question": " \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Can you speak slower, please?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0634"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "question": " \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Can you speak slower, please?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u064a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "question": " \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0628\u0628\u0637\u0621\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Can you speak slower, please?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Can you say that in English?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0631\u0631\u0647\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "question": " \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644\u0647\u0627 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Can you say that in English?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0628\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Do you speak English?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a",
      "question": " \u0628\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0628\u062a\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0645 \u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Do you speak English?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u064a\u0647",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0648 ... \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0625\u064a\u0647 \u0647\u0648 ... \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "What is ... in Arabic?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u064a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "question": " \u0625\u064a\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f ... \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0625\u064a\u0647 \u0647\u0648 ... \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "What is ... in Arabic?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u064a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629",
      "question": " \u0625\u064a\u0647 \u0647\u0648 ... \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0625\u064a\u0647 \u0647\u0648 ... \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "What is ... in Arabic?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u064a\u0647",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0647\u0648 ... \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0625\u064a\u0647 \u0647\u0648 ... \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "What is ... in English?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0648",
      "question": " \u0625\u064a\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f ... \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0625\u064a\u0647 \u0647\u0648 ... \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "What is ... in English?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0647"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629",
      "question": " \u0625\u064a\u0647 \u0647\u0648 ... \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0625\u064a\u0647 \u0647\u0648 ... \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "What is ... in English?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f ... \u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f ... \u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "sentence_en": "One ... , please",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "question": " \u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f ... \u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f ... \u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "sentence_en": "One ... , please",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "question": " \u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f ... \u060c \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f ... \u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "sentence_en": "One ... , please",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0641\u0633",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0646\u0641\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "sentence_en": "The same for me",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621",
      "question": " \u0646\u0641\u0633 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0646\u0641\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "sentence_en": "The same for me",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "question": " \u0646\u0641\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0646\u0641\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u0634\u064a\u0621 \u0644\u064a\u0627",
      "sentence_en": "The same for me",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u064a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0647",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u064a\u0647\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062f\u0647 \u0625\u064a\u0647\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "What is this?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u064a\u0647"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u064a\u0647",
      "question": " \u062f\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062f\u0647 \u0625\u064a\u0647\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "What is this?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0647",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062f\u0647 \u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Is this vegetarian?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u064a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a",
      "question": " \u062f\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062f\u0647 \u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Is this vegetarian?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0627\u0646\u064a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f ... \u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643 ... \u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Do you have ... ?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "sentence_en": "The menu, please",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "question": " \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "sentence_en": "The menu, please",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "question": " \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0626\u0645\u0629\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "sentence_en": "The menu, please",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0634",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0645\u0634 \u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "sentence_en": "Not very spicy, please",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0634"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629",
      "question": " \u0645\u0634 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0645\u0634 \u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "sentence_en": "Not very spicy, please",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0634"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631",
      "question": " \u0645\u0634 \u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0645\u0634 \u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "sentence_en": "Not very spicy, please",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "question": " \u0645\u0634 \u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0645\u0634 \u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "sentence_en": "Not very spicy, please",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "question": " \u0645\u0634 \u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0645\u0634 \u062d\u0627\u0631\u0629 \u0643\u062a\u064a\u0631\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "sentence_en": "Not very spicy, please",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a\u0629\u060c \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629\u060c \u0645\u0639 \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a\u0629\u060c \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629\u060c \u0645\u0639 \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "sentence_en": "Two Turkish coffee, light, with a bit of sugar",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629",
      "question": " \u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a\u0629\u060c \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629\u060c \u0645\u0639 \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a\u0629\u060c \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629\u060c \u0645\u0639 \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "sentence_en": "Two Turkish coffee, light, with a bit of sugar",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a\u0629",
      "question": " \u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u060c \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629\u060c \u0645\u0639 \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a\u0629\u060c \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629\u060c \u0645\u0639 \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "sentence_en": "Two Turkish coffee, light, with a bit of sugar",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0627\u0646\u064a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629",
      "question": " \u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a\u0629\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f\u060c \u0645\u0639 \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a\u0629\u060c \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629\u060c \u0645\u0639 \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "sentence_en": "Two Turkish coffee, light, with a bit of sugar",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062e\u064a\u0631"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0639",
      "question": " \u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a\u0629\u060c \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a\u0629\u060c \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629\u060c \u0645\u0639 \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "sentence_en": "Two Turkish coffee, light, with a bit of sugar",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u0647"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629",
      "question": " \u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a\u0629\u060c \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629\u060c \u0645\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a\u0629\u060c \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629\u060c \u0645\u0639 \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "sentence_en": "Two Turkish coffee, light, with a bit of sugar",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u064a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "question": " \u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a\u0629\u060c \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629\u060c \u0645\u0639 \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0625\u062a\u0646\u064a\u0646 \u0642\u0647\u0648\u0629 \u062a\u0631\u0643\u064a\u0629\u060c \u062e\u0641\u064a\u0641\u0629\u060c \u0645\u0639 \u0634\u0648\u064a\u0629 \u0633\u0643\u0631",
      "sentence_en": "Two Turkish coffee, light, with a bit of sugar",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0623\u0643\u0644"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Can I pay with card?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u064a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639",
      "question": " \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Can I pay with card?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u064a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629",
      "question": " \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062f\u0641\u0639 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Can I pay with card?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "sentence_en": "The bill, please",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "question": " \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "sentence_en": "The bill, please",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "question": " \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u062a\u0648\u0631\u0629\u060c \u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643",
      "sentence_en": "The bill, please",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643 \u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Do you have anything vegetarian?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "question": " \u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643 \u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Do you have anything vegetarian?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a",
      "question": " \u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643 \u0623\u0643\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0639\u0646\u062f\u0643 \u0623\u0643\u0644 \u0646\u0628\u0627\u062a\u064a\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Do you have anything vegetarian?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0634"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u062d\u0635",
      "question": " (\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646) \u0643\u0644 \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " (\u0641\u062d\u0635 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646) \u0643\u0644 \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "(Security Check) Is everything alright?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646",
      "question": " (\u0641\u062d\u0635 \u061f\u061f\u061f) \u0643\u0644 \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " (\u0641\u062d\u0635 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646) \u0643\u0644 \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "(Security Check) Is everything alright?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0644",
      "question": " (\u0641\u062d\u0635 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646) \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " (\u0641\u062d\u0635 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646) \u0643\u0644 \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "(Security Check) Is everything alright?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u064a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629",
      "question": " (\u0641\u062d\u0635 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646) \u0643\u0644 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " (\u0641\u062d\u0635 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646) \u0643\u0644 \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "(Security Check) Is everything alright?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "question": " (\u0641\u062d\u0635 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646) \u0643\u0644 \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " (\u0641\u062d\u0635 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646) \u0643\u0644 \u062d\u0627\u062c\u0629 \u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "(Security Check) Is everything alright?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0634"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u062d\u0635",
      "question": " (\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646) \u062f\u064a \u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f \u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "sentence_ar": " (\u0641\u062d\u0635 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646) \u062f\u064a \u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f \u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "sentence_en": "(Security Check) This is just food",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646",
      "question": " (\u0641\u062d\u0635 \u061f\u061f\u061f) \u062f\u064a \u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f \u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "sentence_ar": " (\u0641\u062d\u0635 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646) \u062f\u064a \u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f \u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "sentence_en": "(Security Check) This is just food",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u064a",
      "question": " (\u0641\u062d\u0635 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646) \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f \u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "sentence_ar": " (\u0641\u062d\u0635 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646) \u062f\u064a \u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f \u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "sentence_en": "(Security Check) This is just food",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f",
      "question": " (\u0641\u062d\u0635 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646) \u062f\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "sentence_ar": " (\u0641\u062d\u0635 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646) \u062f\u064a \u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f \u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "sentence_en": "(Security Check) This is just food",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "question": " (\u0641\u062d\u0635 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646) \u062f\u064a \u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " (\u0641\u062d\u0635 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0646) \u062f\u064a \u0645\u062c\u0631\u062f \u0623\u0643\u0644",
      "sentence_en": "(Security Check) This is just food",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0627\u0643\u0644"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062a\u0641\u0636\u0644",
      "sentence_en": "Here you go (showing something)",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "question": " (\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629) \u0623\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " (\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629) \u0623\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "(Pool) Which lanes are free?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0645"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629",
      "question": " (\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u061f\u061f\u061f) \u0623\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " (\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629) \u0623\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "(Pool) Which lanes are free?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0642\u0629"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u064a\u0647",
      "question": " (\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629) \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " (\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629) \u0623\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "(Pool) Which lanes are free?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u064a\u0647"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646",
      "question": " (\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629) \u0623\u064a\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " (\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629) \u0623\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "(Pool) Which lanes are free?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629",
      "question": " (\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629) \u0623\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " (\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0627\u062d\u0629) \u0623\u064a\u0647 \u0627\u0644\u0623\u0645\u0627\u0643\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0636\u064a\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "(Pool) Which lanes are free?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0645\u0643\u064a\u0641"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u062d\u062f",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u062a\u0649 \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0644\u062d\u062f \u0645\u062a\u0649 \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "How long is it open?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u062a\u0649",
      "question": " \u0644\u062d\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0644\u062d\u062f \u0645\u062a\u0649 \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "How long is it open?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d",
      "question": " \u0644\u062d\u062f \u0645\u062a\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0644\u062d\u062f \u0645\u062a\u0649 \u0645\u0641\u062a\u0648\u062d\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "How long is it open?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0647",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u064a",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062f\u0647 \u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u064a",
      "sentence_en": "Here is my homework",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u064a\u0647"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u064a",
      "question": " \u062f\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062f\u0647 \u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u064a",
      "sentence_en": "Here is my homework",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0641\u064a \u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Do we have homework?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628",
      "question": " \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0641\u064a \u0648\u0627\u062c\u0628\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Do we have homework?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u0627\u0647\u0645"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f ... \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 ... \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Where is room ... ?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646",
      "question": " \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 ... \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0627\u0644\u063a\u0631\u0641\u0629 ... \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Where is room ... ?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "sentence_en": "I need to go to the bathroom",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c",
      "question": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "sentence_en": "I need to go to the bathroom",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0634"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "question": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0645\u062d\u062a\u0627\u062c \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0645\u0627\u0645",
      "sentence_en": "I need to go to the bathroom",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0635\u0628\u062d",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062a\u0635\u0628\u062d \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "sentence_en": "Good Night",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0644\u0649",
      "question": " \u062a\u0635\u0628\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062a\u0635\u0628\u062d \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "sentence_en": "Good Night",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "question": " \u062a\u0635\u0628\u062d \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062a\u0635\u0628\u062d \u0639\u0644\u0649 \u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "sentence_en": "Good Night",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "How are you?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u064a\u0647"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u060c \u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u060c \u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "I'm good, how are you?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "question": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u060c \u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u060c \u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "I'm good, how are you?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0634"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643",
      "question": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u060c \u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "I'm good, how are you?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u064a\u0647"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0628\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Do you live in Cairo?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "question": " \u0628\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0628\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Do you live in Cairo?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629",
      "question": " \u0628\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0628\u062a\u0633\u0643\u0646 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0647\u0631\u0629\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Do you live in Cairo?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u062a\u0643",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a \u0628\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u062a\u0643",
      "sentence_en": "Nice to meet you",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0643\u0631"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u062a\u0643",
      "question": " \u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062a\u0634\u0631\u0641\u062a \u0628\u0645\u0639\u0631\u0641\u062a\u0643",
      "sentence_en": "Nice to meet you",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0633\u0645\u0643",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u064a\u0647\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0625\u0633\u0645\u0643 \u0625\u064a\u0647\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "What's your name?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0632\u064a\u0643"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u064a\u0647",
      "question": " \u0625\u0633\u0645\u0643 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0625\u0633\u0645\u0643 \u0625\u064a\u0647\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "What's your name?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u0625\u0644\u0649 ... \u0643\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u0625\u0644\u0649 ... \u0643\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "How much is a ticket to ... ?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0627\u0643\u0644"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629",
      "question": " \u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 ... \u0643\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u0625\u0644\u0649 ... \u0643\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "How much is a ticket to ... ?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0643\u0631"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "question": " \u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f ... \u0643\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u0625\u0644\u0649 ... \u0643\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "How much is a ticket to ... ?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u064a\u0647"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0645",
      "question": " \u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u0625\u0644\u0649 ... \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u062a\u0643\u0644\u0641\u0629 \u062a\u0630\u0643\u0631\u0629 \u0625\u0644\u0649 ... \u0643\u0627\u0645\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "How much is a ticket to ... ?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u0646\u0627",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0641\u064a \u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629\u060c \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0641\u064a \u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629\u060c \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "I study at an Egyptian university, do I get the Egyptian price?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633",
      "question": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a \u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629\u060c \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0641\u064a \u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629\u060c \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "I study at an Egyptian university, do I get the Egyptian price?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a",
      "question": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629\u060c \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0641\u064a \u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629\u060c \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "I study at an Egyptian university, do I get the Egyptian price?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629",
      "question": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0641\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629\u060c \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0641\u064a \u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629\u060c \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "I study at an Egyptian university, do I get the Egyptian price?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0645"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629",
      "question": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0641\u064a \u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u060c \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0641\u064a \u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629\u060c \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "I study at an Egyptian university, do I get the Egyptian price?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u064a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631",
      "question": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0641\u064a \u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629\u060c \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0641\u064a \u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629\u060c \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "I study at an Egyptian university, do I get the Egyptian price?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628",
      "question": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0641\u064a \u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629\u060c \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0641\u064a \u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629\u060c \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "I study at an Egyptian university, do I get the Egyptian price?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u064a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0639\u0631",
      "question": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0641\u064a \u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629\u060c \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0641\u064a \u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629\u060c \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "I study at an Egyptian university, do I get the Egyptian price?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0643\u0631"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631",
      "question": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0641\u064a \u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u064a\u0629\u060c \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0633\u0639\u0631 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0623\u0646\u0627 \u0628\u062f\u0631\u0633 \u0641\u064a \u062c\u0627\u0645\u0639\u0629 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u064a\u0629\u060c \u0647\u0642\u062f\u0631 \u0623\u062c\u064a\u0628 \u0633\u0639\u0631 \u0645\u0635\u0631\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "I study at an Egyptian university, do I get the Egyptian price?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0643\u0631"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062f\u0647 \u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 ... \u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633 \u062f\u0647 \u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 ... \u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Does this bus go to ... ?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0647",
      "question": " \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 ... \u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633 \u062f\u0647 \u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 ... \u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Does this bus go to ... ?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u064a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d",
      "question": " \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633 \u062f\u0647 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0625\u0644\u0649 ... \u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633 \u062f\u0647 \u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 ... \u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Does this bus go to ... ?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649",
      "question": " \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633 \u062f\u0647 \u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f ... \u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0627\u0644\u0623\u062a\u0648\u0628\u064a\u0633 \u062f\u0647 \u0628\u064a\u0631\u0648\u062d \u0625\u0644\u0649 ... \u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Does this bus go to ... ?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u064a\u0647"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u0645\u062a",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0646\u0645\u062a \u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Did you sleep well?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0645\u062d\u062a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633",
      "question": " \u0646\u0645\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0646\u0645\u062a \u0643\u0648\u064a\u0633\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Did you sleep well?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u064a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0627\u0643\u0644\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u062a\u0627\u0643\u0644\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Do you want to eat?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u064a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0627\u0643\u0644",
      "question": " \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u062a\u0627\u0643\u0644\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Do you want to eat?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0627\u0646\u064a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0645\u0646 \u062f\u0647\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u0645\u0646 \u062f\u0647\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Do you want some of this?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0646",
      "question": " \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062f\u0647\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u0645\u0646 \u062f\u0647\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Do you want some of this?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0645\u0635\u0631"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0647",
      "question": " \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u0645\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632 \u0645\u0646 \u062f\u0647\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Do you want some of this?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u064a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0646",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0646 \u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Do you want to get lunch?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0628\u0641\u064a\u0632\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649",
      "question": " \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0639\u0627\u064a\u0632\u064a\u0646 \u0646\u062a\u063a\u062f\u0649\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Do you want to get lunch?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062f\u064a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0625\u0646\u062a",
      "question": " \u061f\u061f\u061f \u062c\u0648\u0639\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0625\u0646\u062a \u062c\u0648\u0639\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Are you hungry?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0644\u0649"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062c\u0648\u0639\u0627\u0646",
      "question": " \u0625\u0646\u062a \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": " \u0625\u0646\u062a \u062c\u0648\u0639\u0627\u0646\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Are you hungry?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0634"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "sentence_ar": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "sentence_en": "good morning",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "question": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "sentence_en": "good morning",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631",
      "sentence_ar": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631",
      "sentence_en": "answer to \"good morning\"",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0643\u0627\u0634"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631",
      "question": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": "\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0646\u0648\u0631",
      "sentence_en": "answer to \"good morning\"",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0633\u0627",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0633\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "sentence_en": "good evening",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "question": "\u0645\u0633\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0633\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",
      "sentence_en": "good evening",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062e\u064a\u0631"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0627\u0646\u064a",
      "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0627\u0646\u064a",
      "sentence_en": "again, please",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0643\u0631"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0627\u0646\u064a",
      "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0627\u0646\u064a",
      "sentence_en": "again, please",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0627\u0643\u0644"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0644\u0648",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0633\u0645\u062d\u062a",
      "sentence_ar": "\u0644\u0648 \u0633\u0645\u062d\u062a",
      "sentence_en": "please",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0639\u0641\u0648"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0633\u0645\u062d\u062a",
      "question": "\u0644\u0648 \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": "\u0644\u0648 \u0633\u0645\u062d\u062a",
      "sentence_en": "please",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0633\u0643\u0631"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062f\u0627",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u0631\u0627\u064a\u062d \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": "\u062f\u0627 \u0631\u0627\u064a\u062d \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Where is this going?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u062f\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0631\u0627\u064a\u062d",
      "question": "\u062f\u0627 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": "\u062f\u0627 \u0631\u0627\u064a\u062d \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Where is this going?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0641\u064a\u0646",
      "question": "\u062f\u0627 \u0631\u0627\u064a\u062d \u061f\u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": "\u062f\u0627 \u0631\u0627\u064a\u062d \u0641\u064a\u0646\u061f",
      "sentence_en": "Where is this going?",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0644\u064a\u0627"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646",
      "question": "\u061f\u061f\u061f \u062a\u0646\u0631\u0644\u0646\u064a \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0640\u0640\u0640",
      "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0631\u0644\u0646\u064a \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0640\u0640\u0640",
      "sentence_en": "Drop me off at ...",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062a\u0645\u0627\u0645"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u062a\u0646\u0631\u0644\u0646\u064a",
      "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0640\u0640\u0640",
      "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0631\u0644\u0646\u064a \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0640\u0640\u0640",
      "sentence_en": "Drop me off at ...",
      "wrong_answer": "\u0625\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0639\u0646\u062f",
      "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0631\u0644\u0646\u064a \u061f\u061f\u061f \u0640\u0640\u0640",
      "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0631\u0644\u0646\u064a \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0640\u0640\u0640",
      "sentence_en": "Drop me off at ...",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Choose the word that best completes the sentence:",
      "correct_answer": "\u0640\u0640\u0640",
      "question": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0631\u0644\u0646\u064a \u0639\u0646\u062f \u061f\u061f\u061f",
      "sentence_ar": "\u0645\u0645\u0643\u0646 \u062a\u0646\u0631\u0644\u0646\u064a \u0639\u0646\u062f \u0640\u0640\u0640",
      "sentence_en": "Drop me off at ...",
      "wrong_answer": "\u062c\u064a\u062f"
    }
  ]
}
